Guide to the James A. Roberts Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1999-290
  - U.S. Agency for International Development Contract Directory 1994 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Proposals 1992: 92046 B&J Landfill (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Proposals 1992: 92047 City of Davis NBD (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Proposals 1992: 92048 Calabasas EIR coordination (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Proposals 1992: 92050 Java City Facilitation (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Proposals 1992: 92053 Idaho IRWA course (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Proposals 1992: 92054 USAEP (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Proposals 1992: 92055 City of Placerville (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Proposals 1992: 92056 SMUD/EDCWA Upper American River Project (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Proposals 1992: 92056 SMUD/EDCWA Upper American River Project (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Proposals 1992: 92058 Senate Office of Research (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Proposals 1992: 92059 UNEX/Environmental Education (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Proposals 1992: 92060 Orange County (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Proposals 1992: 92061 Spanish EIA book (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Proposals 1992: 92062 Davis RFP (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - 0690.20 The Canyon (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - 0690.21 Natoma Lot A (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - 0690.22 Folsom Office (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - 0690.23 Greenback Lane widening (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - 0690.24 K-Mart (Box 103, Folder 20)
  - 0690.25 Legends (Box 103, Folder 21)
  - 0690.19 Alder Creek (Box 103, Folder 22)
  - 0690.19 Alder Creek Annex Management Meeting (Box 103, Folder 23)
  - 0690.19 Alder Creek Technical reports (Box 103, Folder 24)
  - 0690.19 Alder Creek #1 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - 0690.19 Alder Creek #2 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - 0690.19 Alder Creek #3 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - EAFP (City of Folsom East Area Facilities Plan) Plant EIR (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - EAFP General Plan Amendments Resolutions (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - EAFP General Plan Amendments Resolutions (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - EIR examples: Santa Barbara Landfill 1990; Palo Alto Hillview cost proposal; Altamont Landfill 1990; OII Landfill 1990; UCSB LRDP 1990 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - EIR examples: UCSB LRDP 1990; Pacific Texas Pipeline Project DEIR 1985; Tahoe NF 1990 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - EIR examples: El Dorado NF 1982; Deaf Smith Texas 1986; Chevron 1990-1993; Econex conference SMUD 1996 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - NAEP election 1996 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - NAEP election 1996 ballots (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Data Notebook, Geologic Hazard Areas (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Operation Swamp Fox, Geographic Factors 1961 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - CEQA: Standard CEQA forms (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Geography Journals 1993 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Analysis for Transportation Plans 1974 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Keelung (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Nevada City Master Environmental Inventory (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous reports, other publications (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Nevada County General Plan: Administration 1992 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Nevada County General Plan: Background info (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Nevada County General Plan: General notes (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Nevada County General Plan: EIR/CEQA (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Nevada County General Plan: Team meeting notes (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Nevada County General Plan: MEA general (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Nevada County General Plan: County File information (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Nevada County General Plan: Steering committee (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Nevada County General Plan: Steering committee (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Nevada County General Plan: Land use projections (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Nevada County General Plan: Minerals Management (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Nevada County General Plan: Truckee Committee plan (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Nevada County General Plan: OPR extension (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Nevada County General Plan: Waste management (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Nevada County General Plan: Archeological/Cultural resources (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Nevada County General Plan: Truckee (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - Nevada County General Plan: Telecommuting (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - Nevada County General Plan: Earth (geology) (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - Nevada County General Plan: Meterology/Air Quality (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - Nevada County General Plan: correspondence out (Box 108, Folder 20)
  - Nevada County General Plan: correspondence in (Box 108, Folder 21)
  - SMUD conference 1996 (Box 108, Folder 22)
  - SMUD conference 1996 (Box 108, Folder 23)
  - Pele Defense Fund/CREDAA information 1988 (Box 108, Folder 24)
  - EIR examples: Taiwan (in Chinese) (Box 108, Folder 25)
  - Keelung illustrations (Box 108, Folder 26)
  - Roberts, “Just What is EIR?” Draft 1990 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Argentina: trip report master 1994 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Argentina: Andrea Rodriguez Global (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Argentina: San Martin de los Andes (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Argentina: Environmental Secretariat (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Argentina: Apertura training (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Argentina: Tierra del Fuego (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Argentina: Tahoe-Andes Partnership (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Argentina: General EIA/Environment courses (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Argentina: Bioethics conference 10/1996 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Argentina: FARN general (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Argentina: Follow-up (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Argentina: EIR course materials (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Argentina: miscellaneous publications, correspondence (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Argentina: working notes, general correspondence (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - Argentina: trip report, versions (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - Contra Costa County Landfill reports (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Contra Costa County Landfill reports (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - EAFP binder 1 1992 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - EAFP binder 2a (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - EAFP binder 2b (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Computer software (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous publications, newsletters, reports, memoranda (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Dutch EIR & correspondence (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - EIR examples: Taiwan (In Chinese) (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Taiwan C5 1989 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Taiwan D2 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Taiwan C6 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Taiwan C7 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Taiwan D1 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Taiwan Technical Appendices (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Folsom General Plan drafts 1988 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Folsom General Plan EIR (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Folsom General Plan v. 1 Mandatory & Optional elements (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Folsom General Plan v. 2 Technical Appendices (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - North Natomas Community Plan Final EIR 1985 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - North Natomas Community Plan draft (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Sweden: CLAB program 1983-1984 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Sweden: Decision Research (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Sweden: Photographs (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Sweden: Roberts File #1 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Sweden: Roberts file “Siting Heavy Industry” muckup (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Nuclear power reports, other reports 1983-1984 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Nuclear power reports, other reports 1983-1984 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Land use, planning, traffic, development reports (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Swedeplan: coastal industry site (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Hawaii Napali Beach club (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - GEMS accounting: Timesheets 1992 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: A-B (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: C-L (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: M-P (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: R-Z (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - GEMS accounting: Expense sheets 3-4/1992 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Coastlines publications (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Public participation publications (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - EDCWA Draft Final Supplement 1995 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence ending 11/1995 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence ending 2/1996 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence ending 5/1996 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - California State Minority/Women/Disabled Veteran Business Enterprises 1992-1995 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - CRWMP (Civilian Radioactive Waste Management Program) reports (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - CRWMP Nuclear Waste Policy Act (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - EIR examples: Contra Costa Shell 1993; Exxon Refinery Benitez 1993 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - EIR examples: Exxon Refinery Benitez 1993; Chevron; Elsmere Solid Waste Management (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Shell/Chevron miscellaneous correspondence, reports, memoranda (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: Oakridge (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: Ostra Station (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: Portland/Johnson Creek (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: Caltrans (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: Sonoma County Aggregate Resource Management Plan (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: 9109 Italy Course (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: 91024 AID-Eastern Europe (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: 91024 AID-Eastern Europe (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: 91008 Uppsala Motor Sport Arena (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: 91009 Uppsala Rail (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: 91014 Mendocino Landfill (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: 91018 Mendocino Landfill (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: Camp Lejeune (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: Coastal Conservancy (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: Hanford (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: ISRT (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: NBDS Lincoln (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: NPS Course (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: CIWMB RFQ (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: Redwood Landfill (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: Tahoe-Baikal Institute (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: Teichert (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: SHRA SOQ (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - GEMS proposals 1991: Toyon/Bishop Canyon (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - GEI Grants, Fellowships, etc. (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - GEI Grants: Funds and Foundations A-Z (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - GEI: Yolo County Landfill correspondence 1990 (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - GEI: Sonoma County Landfill 1990 (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - GEI: Golden Bear Park 1990 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - GEI: Hayden Hill (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - GEI: OII (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - GEI: Susan Lloyd (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - GEI: International workshop on EM (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - GEI: Altamont Landfill (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 Russell Ranch Specific Plan 1992 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 Folsom invoices 1992 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 General Environmental Coordination (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.01 EAFP (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.02 Silverbrook (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.03 Reflections 1&2 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.04 Santa Fe (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.05 Broadstone (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.06 Silverbrook (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.07 Windstar (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.08 Creekside (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.09 Blue Ravine (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.10 Willow Springs (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.11 Old Town (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.12 Sun Country (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.13 Cobble hills (Box 119, Folder 22)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.14 Task 14 (Box 119, Folder 23)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.15 Natoma Lot G (Box 119, Folder 24)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.17 Natoma Lot J (Box 119, Folder 25)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.19 Alder Creek (Box 119, Folder 26)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.20 Canyon (Box 119, Folder 27)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.21 Natoma Lot A (Box 119, Folder 28)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.23 Greenback (Box 119, Folder 29)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.24 K-Mart (Box 119, Folder 30)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.25 Legends (Box 119, Folder 31)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.26 Lakeside Memorial (Box 119, Folder 32)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.27 Snack Shack (Box 119, Folder 33)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690.28 Albertsons (Box 119, Folder 34)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-2 Sphere of Influence (Box 119, Folder 35)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-3 Blue Ravine Oaks (Box 119, Folder 36)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-4 Bridge EIR (Box 119, Folder 37)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-5 Broadstone II (Box 119, Folder 38)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-6 Mitigation Monitoring (Box 119, Folder 39)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-7 Humbug (Box 119, Folder 40)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-8 East Area Coordination (Box 119, Folder 41)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-9 Teichert (Box 119, Folder 42)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-13 Athletic Club (Box 119, Folder 43)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-14 HEV (Box 119, Folder 44)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-15 Folsom Dam Reopening (Box 119, Folder 45)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-16 Business Center (Box 119, Folder 46)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-17 Sacramento Savings (Box 119, Folder 47)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-18 Los Cerros (Box 119, Folder 48)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-19 ARC (Box 119, Folder 49)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-20 Willow Creek Estates (Box 119, Folder 50)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-23 Greenback Bike Lanes (Box 119, Folder 51)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 922-24 Household Hazardous Waste (Box 119, Folder 52)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-25 Lexington (Box 119, Folder 53)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-26 Oakhill Church (Box 119, Folder 54)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-27 Intel (Box 119, Folder 55)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00690 92-28 Natoma Lot M (Box 119, Folder 56)
  - 7023 MCP .37-.47 File Index (Box 119, Folder 57)
  - 7023.37 Land Use Permit (Box 119, Folder 58)
  - 7023.38 East Diablo Fire Protection District (Box 119, Folder 59)
  - 7023.39 Design Review Meeting 1990 (Box 119, Folder 60)
  - 7023.40 U.S. COE pre-application notification (Box 119, Folder 61)
  - 7023.42 U.S, COE permit application 7/1990 (Box 119, Folder 62)
  - 7023.42 Nationwide (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - 7023.44 COE #1 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - 7023.45 COE #2 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - 7023.46 San Joaquin Kit Fox Biological Assessment (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - 7023.47 EBPRD (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - RMP (South Fork American River Management Plan) meetings 1996-1998 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - RMP: drafts, working documents 1996-1997 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - RMP: contractual documents 1996-1998 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - RMP: Management Plan 1982 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - RMP: Environmental Report 1982 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - El Dorado Interim River Management Plan 1980 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - El Dorado River Management Plan Phase I Report 1996 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous bound volumes (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Sweden: Svenska Technical reports (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Sweden/Scandinavia publications (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Taiwan publications (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Climate Control Project 1949-1952 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Dutch Exchange Coordination 1980 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Sacramento Keifer Landfill EIR 1998 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Alder Creek Hydrology report 1998 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - City of Folsom Sphere of Influence Amendment 1998 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 4-6/1998 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 7-8/1998 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 8-9/1998 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 10/1998 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - California Heritage Preservation commission 1997-1998 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 1-2/1999 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 10-11/1998 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 11-12/1998 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Roberts miscellaneous proposals & projects 1998: SAIC (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: UCSB 4/1998 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Jeannie Hanford property (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: PSOMAS (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Capitol Region Institute 1998 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: N.C. Department of Transportation (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Placer County EIRs (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Governor’s Environmental Goals correspondence 1983-1984 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: California Student aid Committee (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Bilheimer project 1997-1998 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: GEI to-dos 1997 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Alejandro discussion (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Save the Children (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Roberts-Golder 1997 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Cook Islands Suwarrow Island Project (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Hai Nan (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: 97012 Intranest Squaw CEQA (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Shih-Liang Tu (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: River Fields (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Pipeline Project-Lemos (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Truckee seamless education (Box 124, Folder 21)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Faith, Justice & a Healthy World (Box 124, Folder 22)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Sacramento Watershed Public Education (Box 124, Folder 23)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: NEPA- Global impact (Box 124, Folder 24)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: 97024 Sydkraft (Box 124, Folder 25)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: South Coast Air Quality CEQA (Box 124, Folder 26)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Tsunami (Box 124, Folder 27)
  - Roberts miscellaneous projects: Grishin Fulbright (Box 124, Folder 28)
  - AEP & NAEP serials 1997-1998 (Box 124, Folder 29)
  - NAEP presidential correspondence 7/1998 (Box 124, Folder 30)
  - NAEP presidential correspondence 9-11/1998 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - NAEP presidential correspondence 11/1998-1/1999 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - NAEP presidential correspondence 11/1998 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - NAEP presidential correspondence: San Diego Site Visit 1997 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - NAEP presidential correspondence: Andy McCusker (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - NAEP presidential correspondence: Board 1997-1998 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - NAEP presidential correspondence: Executive committee 7/1997 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - NAEP presidential correspondence: Project XL (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - NAEP presidential correspondence: Environmental Business Summit 5/1997 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - NAEP presidential correspondence: Board Meetings 1999 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - NAEP conference proceedings & abstracts 1997-1999 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - NAEP conference 1998 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - NAEP legal counsel (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - NAEP Colorado Springs workshop (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - NAEP California Chapter (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - NEPA iso14000 sustainable development (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - EPA publications (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - NEPA update 1997-1998 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - NAEP board meeting 5/1996 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - NAEP board meeting 9/1996 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - NAEP board meeting 12/1996 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - NAEP board meeting 3/1997 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - NAEP board meeting 5/1997 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - NAEP board meeting 9/1997 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - NAEP board meeting 12/1997 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - NAEP board meeting 3/1998 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - NAEP board meeting 6/1998 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - NAEP board meeting 8/1998 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - NAEP board meeting 12/1998 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - NAEP board meeting 3/1999 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - CVP (Central Valley Project Improvement Act) DEIS, 9 Volumes & Appendices 1-4 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - CVP DEIS Appendices 5-9 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - 01493.A Taiwan Coastal Planning & Management 1993-1994 File Index (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - 01493.00.000 General (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - 01493.00.001 correspondence in (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - 01493.00.002 Correspondence out (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - 01493.00.100 Proposal #1 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - 01493.00.100 Proposal #2 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - 01493.00.100q Key People (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - 01493.00.100b UTEC Qualifications (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - 01493.00.110 Contract (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - 01493.00.401 Rules (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - 01493.00.402 Articles/Research (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - 01493 Chronological correspondence Memoranda re: Zoning (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - 01493 Phase I Report Master 1992 (Box 128, Folder 14)
  - 01493 Land Use Suitability master (Box 128, Folder 15)
  - 01493 Miscellaneous reports (mostly in Chinese) (Box 128, Folder 16)
  - 01493.00.501 Regional Maps (Box 128, Folder 17)
  - 01493 Miscellaneous correspondence & memoranda (Box 128, Folder 18)
  - 01493 Preliminary OCS Analysis 1992 (Box 128, Folder 19)
  - MCP Revised Project Description v.1-3 1989 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - MCP Project Description v.1 1988 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Sherwin Ski Area EIS 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - IIE Conference 8/1991 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Tahoe National forest Reports, Maps 1981-1990 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Iceland/Denmark Sacramento Visit 9/1991 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Battelle RFP 1986 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Battelle Pacific NW Laboratory 1986 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Willow Springs 8/1991 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Folsom General Plan 1987-1988 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - EIR examples: Los Rios Community College; Folsom Lake 1990 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Broadstone II Master Plan EIR proposed final 7/1992 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Broadstone Master Plan EIR Administrative Final 6/1992 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Broadstone Master Plan EIR final 5/1991 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Broadstone Master Plan EIR Technical Appendices 12/1990 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - EAFP reports 1990-1992 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Coastal Management publications 1975-1986 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - California Coastal Commission reports 1983-1993 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Mining & Processing Wastes 1990 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Toxic Air Pollutants Source Assessment Manual 1987 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - MCP Preliminary Arborist’s Reports (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Effects & Impacts Table Draft 1991 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Sacramento Systems Planning Transit Study 1991 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - EIR handbooks: Environmental Data Notebook- Scenic, Scientific, Recreational, & Educational Resource Areas 1975 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - EIR examples: Prairie City Center EIR 1992; Willow Springs EIR 1991 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - EAFP draft 8/1991 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - American River Bridge Crossing Project DEIR 3/1992 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Broadstone Master Development Plan 2/1989 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Broadstone DEIR Final Administrative 5/1991 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Broadstone II Master Development Plan 9/1991 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Broadstone III Specific Plan EIR 3/1991 (Box 131, Folder 10)